https://popsicube-fovea.com/gdpr-privacy-notice/

GDPR & Privacy Notice
Information Collection, Use, Management and Sharing of your Personnal Data by PopsiCube Group
What do we need ?
The PopsiCube Group will be known as the ‘Controller’ of your personal data regarding business partnership (limited to your professional contact details and your position within your Company), required as part of our commercial activity. According to the GDPR the processing of personal data for direct marketing purposes may be considered as carried out for a legitimate interest, and so is considered as lawful.
Why do we need it ?
We are the sole owner of the information collected on this website. We only have access to and collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than needed to fulfil your request, e.g. to be part of an investigative site for a potential clinical study.
We need to know this basic personal data in order to be able to respond you regarding the reason you contacted us, and to contact you as part of our commercial activity and market research that may interest you regarding your job position inside your Company. We will not collect any personal data from you we do not need for this purpose.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about potential services, collaborations, or changes to this privacy notice.
What do we do with it ?
All the personal data we process is processed internally by our staff in France. Therefore, for the purposes of IT hosting and maintenance this information is located on secured external servers located in France.
Your data will not be transferred to any recipient in a third country or international organisation. No third parties have access to your personal data unless the law allows them to do so.
We have procedure and policy regarding Information Security and Data Protection in place to oversee the effective and secure processing of your personal data. Your data will not be subject to automated decision-making, including profiling.
How is your information protected ?
We take precautions to protect your information. Wherever we collect sensitive information, it is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, recruitment’s site) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers and servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
How long do we keep it
Your information that may be used for marketing and prospection purposes will be kept with us until you notify us that you no longer wish to receive this information, and at the latest, at the end of the activity of the company.
What are your rights?
In line with the GDPR, you can exercise your right regarding your personal data at any time via phone, email or our postal address: the right to access to, to ask for rectification, erasure or restriction of processing and to object to processing, as well as the right to data portability.
If you wish to raise a complaint on how we have handled your personal data, you can contact our Data Protection Officer using the following address dpo@popsicube.com who will investigate the matter.
If you are not satisfied with our response or if you believe we are processing your personal data not in accordance with the law you can complain to the CNIL (French Supervisory Authority).
PopsiCube Group
6 rue Jean-Pierre Timbaud
Le Campus – Bât A1 Sud
78180 Montigny le Bretonneux
FRANCE
Phone : 01 80 90 50 80
Fax : 01 80 90 50 89
Email : dpo@popsicube.com
Popular Post
Popsi Cube sponsor of the 2nd Kiev Clinical Research Forum 16-17 May 2019.
19 Dec 2018
FORUM FRANCO-QUEBECOIS innovation en santé Medicen Paris May 15-16 2018 2nd edition
15 May 2018
PopsiCube acquires FOVEA Group CRO
01 Jun 2017
E2MAO study publication
09 Jun 2017
PopsiCube-FOVEA @ DIA 2017 Chicago
16 Jun 2017
SNITEM the 4th edition of the Innovative Start-up day for the medical device
Paris June 6th 2018
06 Jun 2018
MEDICEN Commission DAS Santé Numérique 4 septembre 2018
04 Sep 2018
EM-Phases PRAGUE 22-23 OCTOBER 2018
26 Oct 2018
2017 WUHAN Convention on Innovative therapeutics for Cancer and Ageing diseases
14 Oct 2017
Popsi Cube sponsor of the 8th Day of Clinical Research next January 31
21 Nov 2018
Categories
Clinical Research Services
Company Life
Conference & Exhibition
TagsCampus
Exhibition
+33(0)1.80.90.50.80
Mon - Fri 8.30 - 18.30
1st floor, 6 rue Jean Pierre Timbaud
78180 Montigny-le-Bretonneux, France
info@popsicube-fovea.com
We have a unique profile for a CRO providing distinctive and innovative dual expertise by combining clinical research implementation with the development
of customized IT applications specific to the pharmaceutical industry.
Copyright © 2017 PopsiCube-Fovea. all rights reserved.
